sixflags.com 2019-05-28

# Privacy Policy | Six Flags

_Effective date: November 6, 2018_

This Privacy Policy governs websites and mobile applications owned and operated by Six Flags Entertainment Corporation (“Six Flags,” “we,” “us,” and “our”), including sixflags.com (the “Website”) and the Six Flags Mobile Application (the “App” and together with the Website, the “Site”). 

To jump to a particular section, click on the relevant link. Otherwise, scroll down to read the entire Policy.

  * Scope of This Policy
  * Your Consent
  * Our Terms of Use
  * Your Choices
  * Location Data
  * Information We Collect
  * Information About Third-Party Cookies
  * How We Use Your Information
  * How We Share Your Information
  * How We Protect Your Information
  * Employment Applications
  * A Note About Children's Privacy
  * Links To Other Websites
  * Access to Your Information
  * Website Hosting Location
  * Governing Law
  * This Policy May Change
  * Questions About This policy

## Scope of This Policy

Six Flags collects certain information about or related to you through this Site. Some of the information Six Flags collects may be “personal information”—information that identifies you personally, alone or in combination with other information available to us. Six Flags has provided this Privacy Policy so that you will know what information Six Flags collects, how Six Flags uses this information, the types of third parties with whom Six Flags may share this information, and some of the choices that are available to you.

On occasion, Six Flags may offer special programs, activities, events or promotions (collectively, “Special Programs”) that have additional terms, privacy notices and/or consent forms that explain how any personal information you provide will be processed in connection with that program. We recommend you review the terms applicable to those programs before participating.

## Your Consent

By using this Site, you are consenting to the collection, use, disclosure, and transfer of your information as described in this Policy. 

## Our Terms of Use

This Policy is part of the Terms of Use that govern your use of this Site. A link to our Terms of Use is provided at the bottom of each page of this Site.

## Your Choices

 _In General._ We respect your right to make choices about the ways we collect, use, and disclose your information. This Policy describes some of your choices, such as your choice to opt out of receiving “cookies.” We may ask you to indicate your choices at the time and on the page where you provide your information.

_Do Not Track Mechanisms._ California law requires this Policy to address how we respond to any “Do-Not-Track (‘DNT’) signal” delivered by your browser. Because of the changing state of technology and indecision within the industry regarding the meaning of DNT signals, we currently do not make any guarantee that we will honor DNT signals.

_Previously Expressed Preferences._ You may change previously expressed preferences regarding how we use your information. For example, you can opt out of promotional emails we send to you by selecting the “unsubscribe” link located at the bottom of each communication. To change other preferences, please contact us using the information provided below.

## Location Data

When you download the App, we may ask your permission to track your precise, real-time location. If you consent, we may track your location even when you are not using the App. You may change your location-tracking preferences at any time through the settings on your device or through the settings section in the App. Such location-tracking services may be erroneous, inaccurate, incomplete or time-delayed.

## Information We Collect

_Information You Manually Provide._ Six Flags collects the information you manually provide (using your keyboard, mouse, touchpad, or screen) when you use this Site. For example, we collect the information you provide when you communicate with us, purchase tickets, register for a sweepstakes, or otherwise interact with this Site. Some of the information you manually provide may be personal information, such as your name, contact information, photographs, comments, or other content you submit to our Site.

_Information From Third-Party Social Media Platforms._ You may be able to register with, log on to, or enhance your profile on this Site by choosing to automatically populate the requested data fields with information you previously provided to a third-party social media platform (such as Facebook or Twitter). By doing this, you are asking the third-party platform to send us information, including personal information, from your profile on that platform. We treat that information as we do any other information you give to us when you register, log on, or enhance your profile. 

_Information from your browser or device._ Six Flags collects information that is sent to us automatically by your web browser or mobile device. This information typically includes your IP address, the name of your operating system, the name and version of your browser, the date and time of your visit, and the pages you visit. The information we receive may depend on your browser or device settings. 

_The information we receive from your web browser and device is not, in and of itself, personally identifiable._ Generally, we use this information in the aggregate to help us improve this Site and make it more compatible with the technology used by our visitors. However, we may combine it with other information in an attempt to identify you or we may combine it with information that does identify you. We may also review our server logs for security purposes—for example, to detect intrusions into our network—and we might share our server logs, which contain visitors’ IP addresses, with the appropriate investigative authorities who could use that information to trace and identify you.

_Employment Information._ Six Flags collects information about employment applicants as further described in the “Employment Applications” section below.

_Information Collected by Cookies and Other Technologies._ We use “cookies” and other technologies to collect information and support certain features of this Site. For example, we may use these technologies to:

  * collect information about the ways visitors use this Site—which pages you visit, which links you use, and how long you stay on each page;
  * support the features and functionality of this Site—for example, to save you the trouble of reentering information already in our database or to prompt the settings you established on previous visits;
  * personalize your experience when you use this Site; and
  * improve our marketing efforts, including through use of targeted advertising.

We may link the information we collect using cookies and similar technologies to personal information that you provide. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you may set your browser to reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your computer. Although you are not required to accept cookies when you visit this Site, you may be unable to use all of the functionality of this Site if your browser rejects cookies.

## Information About Third-Party Cookies

In addition to the cookies Six Flags delivers to your computer or mobile device through this Site, certain third parties may deliver cookies to you for a variety of reasons. For example, we use Google Analytics, a web analytics tool that helps us understand how visitors engage with our Sites. To learn more about Google Analytics, [click here](https://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html). Other third parties may deliver cookies to your computer or mobile device for the purpose of tracking your online behaviors over time and across nonaffiliated websites and/or delivering targeted advertisements either on this Site or on other websites. You have choices about the collection of information by third parties on our Sites. For example, if you don’t want information about your visit to this Site sent to Google Analytics, you may download an Opt-out Browser Add-on by [clicking here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en). Please note that the Add-on does not prevent information from being sent to Six Flags. In addition, if you would like to opt-out of having interest-based information collected by certain entities during your visits to this Site or other websites, please [click here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). You will be directed to an industry-developed website that contains mechanisms for choosing whether each listed entity may collect and use data for online behavioral advertising purposes. It may be that some of the third parties that collect interest-based information on this Site do not participate in the industry-developed opt-out website, in which case the best way to avoid third-party tracking of your online behaviors may be through your browser settings and deletion of cookies. 

## How We Use Your Information

Generally, we use the information we collect through this Site:

  * to provide the information, products and services you request;
  * to provide you with effective customer service;
  * to provide you with a personalized experience when you use this Site;
  * to contact you with information and notices related to your use of this Site;
  * to contact you with special offers and other information we believe will be of interest to you (in accordance with any privacy preferences you have expressed to us);
  * to invite you to participate in surveys and provide Feedback to us (in accordance with any privacy preferences you have expressed to us);
  * to improve the content, functionality and usability of this Site;
  * to better understand your needs and interests;
  * to improve our products and services;
  * to improve our marketing and promotional efforts;
  * to process employment applications, as further described in the “Employment Applications” section below
  * for security, credit or fraud prevention purposes; and
  * for any other purpose identified in an applicable Privacy Notice, click-through agreement or other agreement between you and us.

## How We Share Your Information

_With Third–Party Vendors._ Six Flags shares information collected through this Site with third-party vendors who act for us or on our behalf. For example, we may use third-party vendors to design and operate this Site; to conduct surveys; and to help us with our promotional efforts. These third-party vendors may need information about you to perform their functions.

_With Other Users of this Site._ You may be able to submit User-Generated Content on or through this Site. Similarly, User-Generated Content that you post on our Facebook page or through Twitter may automatically appear on this Site using functionality made available by those third-party platforms. In this Policy, “User-Generated Content” or “UGC” refers to content that you post using social networking tools and that does not constitute Feedback. Any personal information contained in UGC can be read, collected, or used by others. In addition, we may use UGC you submit for advertising campaigns and other promotions. We may or may not use your name in connection with such use, and we may or may not seek your consent before using the content for such purposes. Therefore, you should have no expectation of privacy with respect to UGC you submit on or through this Site.

_With Third-Party Social Media Platforms._ We may provide functionality on this Site that allows you to automatically post information about the actions you take on this Site to a third-party social media platform (such as Facebook or Twitter). If you choose to take advantage of this functionality, people with access to your profile on the third-party platform may be able to see the actions you have taken—for example, the comments you have posted or the items you have purchased. Thus, you should have no expectation of privacy in those actions. Further, if you choose to link your profile on this Site with an account on a third-party social media platform, we may share the information in your profile with that third-party platform.

_With Other, Carefully Selected Business Partners._ From time to time, we may share your information with selected third parties for their own marketing purposes. For example, we may partner with third parties to sponsor contests or other promotions, and we may share with these third parties the information you submit to us to participate in the contest or take advantage of the promotion. Before doing so, however, we may offer you the opportunity to “opt out” or “opt in,” as required by applicable law. If you do not opt out, your Personal Information will be subject to the information use and sharing practices of the third party, to the extent your information was shared with that third party.

_In aggregate form._ We use information collected through this Site to create a compiled, aggregate (statistical) view of usage patterns. We may share aggregate information about our customers, sales, online traffic patterns and related information to third parties who help us improve our business and services, but these statistics do not include any personally identifiable information. We may provide basic demographic information (gender and age) in conjunction with providing Individualized Data.

_As Part of a Business Transfer._ Your information may be transferred to a successor organization if, for example, we transfer the ownership or operation of this Site to another organization or if we merge with another organization. If such a transfer occurs, the successor organization’s use of your information will be subject to this Policy and the privacy preferences you have expressed to us.

_To Comply with Laws and Protect Our Rights and the Rights of Others._ We may disclose your information when we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with a law, a court order or a subpoena. We may also disclose your information to prevent or investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; to protect the security of this Site; to enforce or apply our online Terms of Use or other agreements; or to protect our own rights or property or the rights, property or safety of our users or others.

_As Described in a Privacy Notice or click-through agreement._ We reserve the right to disclose your information as described in any click–through agreement or any other terms and conditions to which you have agreed.

## How We Protect Your Information

Six Flags takes reasonable precautions to provide a level of security appropriate to the sensitivity of the information we collect. Although we use reasonable measures to help protect your information against unauthorized use or disclosure, we cannot guarantee the security of information provided over the Internet or stored in our databases and will not be responsible for breaches of security beyond our reasonable control.

## Employment Applications 

If you apply for employment with Six Flags via the Site, we will use the information you provide to process your application, to monitor recruitment statistics, and to comply with government reporting requirements. We retain de-identified statistical information about applicants to help inform our recruitment activities. If an applicant becomes a Six Flags employee, Six Flags will maintain a record relating to that person's employment (including information collected via the employment application) and provide additional information about our data practices in connection with employee data to the extent required by law.

## A Note About Children’s Privacy

You must be at least 13 years old to have our permission to use this Site. We do not knowingly collect, use or disclose personal information about visitors under 13 years of age. If you are under the age of 13, you can use this service only in conjunction with your parent’s or guardian’s permission.

## Links to Other Websites

This Policy applies only to this Site. Six Flags and its affiliates may operate many different websites for different purposes and in different countries, where different laws may apply. If you visit another Six Flags website, please take a moment to review the privacy policy posted on that site to learn what information may be collected through that site and how it is processed.

This Site may also contain links to websites that are not operated by Six Flags or its affiliates. These links are provided for your reference and convenience only and do not imply any endorsement of the products sold or information provided through these websites, nor any association with their operators. Six Flags does not control these websites and is not responsible for their data practices. Any information you provide to third parties on their websites is covered under their privacy and data collection policies and is not covered by this Policy. We urge you to review the privacy policy posted on any site you visit before using the site or providing any personal information.

## Access to Your Information

You may have the right to review, correct, update, suppress, restrict or delete personal information that you have previously provided to us. You may also have the right to receive an electronic copy of your personal information for purposes of transmitting it to another company, to the extent this right to data portability is provided to you by law. 

You can contact us about your rights as described above by emailing us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#a3c4d6c6d0d7d1c6cfc2d7cacccdd0e3d0c5d7d38dc0ccce). In your request, please make clear what personal information you would like to access or have changed, whether you would like to have your personal information removed from our database, or other limitations you would like to put on our use of your personal information. We may reject your request, as permitted by applicable law.

We reserve the right to verify your identity in connection with any requests regarding personal information to help ensure that we provide the information to the individual to whom it pertains or his or/her authorized representative. We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable.

Please note that we often need to retain certain information for record keeping purposes and/or to complete any transactions that you began prior to requesting a change or deletion (e.g., when you make a purchase or buy tickets, or enter a promotion, you may not be able to change or delete the information provided until after the completion of such purchase, reservation, or promotion). There may also be residual data that will remain within our databases and other records, which will not be removed. In addition, there may be certain data that we may not allow you to review for legal, security or other reasons.

## Website Hosting Location

Six Flags is a U.S. corporation. The servers that support this Site are located in the United States. While it is in our possession, your information will generally be stored in Six Flags databases or databases maintained by our third-party service providers on servers and data storage devices located in the United States. U.S. data protection laws may not provide as much protection as the data protection laws in force in some other countries, however, we will process your information in accordance with this Policy no matter where our data is stored. If you are located in a country outside the United States, by using this Site you consent to the transfer of your information to the United States.

## California Privacy Rights

Site users who reside in California and have provided their personal information to Six Flags may request information about Six Flags’ disclosures of certain categories of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Such requests must be submitted to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#9ff8eafaecebedfaf3feebf6f0f1ecdfecf9ebefb1fcf0f2). Within thirty days of receiving such a request, Six Flags will provide a list of the categories of personal information disclosed to third parties for third-party direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, along with the names and addresses of these third parties. This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. 

## Governing Law

This Policy shall be governed under the laws of the State of New York, United States of America without regard to any conflict of law principles.

## This Policy May Change

Six Flags reserves the right to update or modify this Policy at any time and without prior notice by posting the revised version of this Policy on this Site.

Your use of this Site following any such change constitutes your agreement that all information collected from or about you after the revised Policy is posted will be subject to the terms of the revised Policy. You may access the current version of this Policy at any time by clicking on the link marked “Privacy” at the bottom of each page of the public areas of this Site.

## Questions About This Policy or Six Flags’ Data Practices

If you have questions or concerns about this Policy, any Privacy Notice, or our data practices, please contact us by email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#b7d0c2d2c4c3c5d2dbd6c3ded8d9c4f7c4d1c3c799d4d8da). You may write to us or contact us via telephone at Six Flags’ corporate offices: 924 Avenue J East, Grand Prairie, Texas 75050 USA; 972-595-5000.
